question_data =  [
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The proof for the Chinese Remainder Theorem used in Number Theory was NOT developed by its first publisher, Sun Tzu.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The &#039;Squaring the Circle&#039; problem is solvable.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "E = MC3",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Zero factorial is equal to zero. ", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "A &#039;Millinillion&#039; is a real number.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "You can square root a negative number with an imaginary number &quot;i&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "An equilateral triangle always has every angle measuring 60&deg;.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
